As you can see, we are level 199 on
Disco Car. So, we are going to play some
games. Let's get into it.
Because they trench stone Jondo.
Let's get into it.
We are on the golden Disco Car because I
recently got the skin maybe like a week
ago and it is absolutely fire.
Just going to slow Jondo off the bat
there.
Ready to shield people just like stay
in position too.
What's going on?
Going to probably have to shield that
chance. I don't know if he has weakness
or not. He might have been gambling.
Yeah, they're on 41 HP. They got bad
people too. They're not even limping
with 41 HP.
What are they doing there? Is that Dude,
I can't tell. I don't know which one's
the footprint animation and the the
spike animation. This chance might be
fried.
Oh, I didn't hit anyone there.
This server is really good by the way.
The
I played like an Australia game against
it and it was really tough. I was able
to win but it was very tough. The
teamwork here is very solid. Oh.
Okay, that's the footprint animation.
Just going to be on standby with my
force field.
So, you hear they're going after
Oh, I was kind of scared they were going
to hit the guest there.
Now, they're still after the 182 chance.
Ooh.
I tried to shield the chance but the
Jane blocked my zap, unfortunately.
Hopefully someone body blocks for the
chance. I'm not going to do it though.
I'm the support. There are lots of
sentinels to do that though.
Especially the guests. Okay, did we miss
the stun?
Nice guest to body block.
Nice body block.
I don't know if the chance Where's the
chance?
Chance is dead. Okay.
One person down.
Probably going after the guest next.
Yeah, that'd be smart.
Oh, I thought that was the spike
animation. Bro, I can't tell I can't
tell the difference between the spike
animation and the freaking footprint
animation.
Okay, let me slow them. After that uh
craft energy.
Very good stuff.
They're probably after the guest right
now, right?
No, they're after Jane. Okay.
Interesting. All right, I got to get out
of here. I'm kind of in a bad position.
Oh.
Okay, just going to stay on standby with
our force field. Well, let some of the
sentinels do
more generators. They might spike that
toward me cuz I'm slowed, but they
don't. They hit the Jane, but I was
shielding, so that reduces some damage.
Oh, that guest.
Oh, dang he went behind the billboard.
I don't know why he went back there
instead of into the team. That sucks.
I like prepared a zap and ooh, that's
really bad. That guy's going to need
help.
Trying to like stun that and knock him
out with that craft energy. No, okay.
I need my shield.
Dang it.
That's the wrong person. Nice.
Okay, I got to get out of here myself.
Kind of low stamina.
So, I tried to zap the guest. There we
go.
Okay, they stunned that, but he gets
unstoppable.
This could be pretty bad. He's stun
immune right now, too. Can't even do
anything.
And the only support it looks like on
this team is actually just all
sentinels.
Maybe not the best team comp.
He might go after me because I'm the
only support.
Where did those spikes go?
Over there?
Who's he after?
He's after
Oh, this Jane keeps body blocking my
zap. That sucks.
Who they after?
That Jane. Oh, that's to be spikes,
right? That is spikes.
Okay, I'll be ready to shield.
Yeah, get out of the corner. Get out of
the corner.
Okay, good stuff. Now they can get to
the team.
Ooh, they ain't looking good.
You can be ready to zap them for some
over shield so they can tank some more
stuff.
Uh, where are they?
Are they over there?
No.
Okay, yes, yes, yes, yes.
They did it. They did it. Okay.
They can tank like another spike. Wait,
what? Did they switch targets?
And there we go. We're good.
Okay, this time we are against guest
666, the best killer currently in the
game, so
could go a bit more differently. I'm
going to be on the generator, but I do
got to be really careful of like a
straight demonic pursuit.
I should probably help someone if they
just got a frontal pride. Yeah, that
noob just got hit with a
um, demonic pursuit by the looks of it,
so they're probably going to need help.
Just going to drop the generator for it.
They just used that, so I'm going to
slow them.
I'm really low stamina. I got to get out
of here.
Okay, we got our stamina back.
Be ready to shield.
I don't know what's really going on over
here.
Okay, nice save. Oh, they didn't miss.
Who did they hit? L7?
Okay, I don't want to go into that
slowness.
Might shield. Yeah, that shield that
guest. Okay, nice. They landed a parry,
though.
Going to slow them again since they used
blood rush.
So, I could kill a little bit of their
momentum, just a little bit.
Ooh.
That's not good.
Oh, the chance just there I think their
gun just misfired too.
Now we're going to need the shield then
probably.
Oh.
Blood hunts. Okay, that's not good.
Since their status
um status effect passive is higher now,
I am going to try to only zap survivors
if possible, but I don't even know where
they are. Oh, there they are. Oh, it's
it's too late.
Okay, I got to get out of here. They're
probably going to go after me.
Dodge that.
It's going to be a bit rough.
Okay, that guy just got slimed.
Totally depends on where they go. Let's
take this medkit.
Yeah, I got to be ready to shield them.
Oh yeah, they missed a block. Oh, wait
no, they hit a fairy. Never mind.
Okay, I got to be ready to zap them
again.
Hey, maybe we got a double zap. We got a
double zap, very good.
Ooh.
Okay, that's not good. I got to hand the
medkit to the vision Lesky.
Oh, they got thrown in the wrong
direction.
I might have to heal this uh I guess
hemorrhage too
if I ever get the chance to.
So then they stop bleeding out and
giving 600 blood.
Lesky's not dead yet.
Going to shield them.
Hopefully they got that pizza.
I got to try to zap them. Oh, never
mind.
Let's get a double zap there.
Try to hand this medkit off to someone
who probably needs it more than me. You
want to heal your wounds?
Oh.
Never mind.
Now we got to help this newb out.
Okay, good stuff.
Hopefully he doesn't see me here.
Okay, he does not. I got to stay safe.
I don't have plasma beam to blood rush
that unfortunately. Or I mean, use
plasma beam on the blood rush
as I usually like to do.
I'm going to get out of here. Double
shield.
Just barely did that.
I'm going to try to get a double zap. Oh
wait, no. Let me just uh zap that uh
guest.
Crap.
My aim was a bit off.
Now, someone's got to help him out.
That's a really good loop against Sixer,
though. Probably the best on this map.
Or one of the best.
Okay, nice.
I have my shield back, so that's really
nice.
Might just use that. They weren't able
to get healed by the pizza because Okay,
they hit their block.
And it is blood hunt time.
Got to stay out of the way of that.
Wait, where did they just go to?
Just going to slow them. I Oh, I missed.
Somehow.
I be
I I was saying like usually in blood
hunt you should try to zap the survivor
over Sixer because he has minus 50%
status effect, but
uh if you can't really aim at the
survivor, then you just hit Sixer cuz
he's big.
And that's another GG's.
Okay, this time we're going against the
slasher
from the best killer to the worst killer
in the game. So,
hopefully this should be pretty light,
but if he focuses some people down
without the team's attention, it could
go wrong. So, let's see how this goes.
I'm going to just wait it out, see where
the slasher comes from so they don't
stealth up on anyone.
Looking at the HP bars right now.
Oh, the builder man is getting got.
Where's the builder man?
So, is that him?
Oh, I tried to get a double zap. That's
kind of greedy.
I'll be ready to shield here, though.
Saving the builder man's life for a
second. Hopefully more sentinels come
and help him out.
So he does not die.
That was very good.
He's getting healed now.
I'm really extending this building man's
lifetime heavy right now.
Just got to keep it up.
I'll try to zap him next. Or actually
the Jane's kind of on him. I'm just
going to go for double zap.
Okay, nice. We landed double zap. It hit
the Shalesky though.
That was not as effective.
Shield him.
Okay, he got at the corner. It's too
late.
Unfortunate.
Just going to make distance here.
What do we have going on here?
Who's getting chased right now?
All right, they got stunned. I'm going
to zap the Anub'arak of it so they have
a little less momentum.
And then my moves are on cool down, so
I'm going to do one generator, but then
get ready to force field again.
Crap, I didn't go to the Shalesky. I
meant to shield the chance cuz I don't
know if he had weakness.
Okay, he does not have weakness
thankfully.
Just going to run away.
Hm.
That's not good.
That's an enraged prophet. Oh gosh.
Uh
I missed. Crap.
Let me try to hand him a medkit. He
might be able to use it at some point.
Come on, pick it up, pick it up, pick it
up.
Ah.
I got a
get out of whatever position I'm in.
It's kind of horrid.
Might shield that Jane in a second.
I'll shield them right now since they
just slowed themselves with the crystal
pitch. Try to maintain their shadow
point so then they can do a shadow heal.
Hopefully.
It doesn't look like their hatchet's on
cool down though.
Let me try to zap
Jane. There we go.
Give them some overheal and speed to
work with.
Ooh, yikes.
W shots done.
Let's see.
Where are they?
Going to need to be ready to shield
here. Oh wait, they got healed. Okay, I
don't need to like as desperately
shield. Still pretty good shield though.
Oh, damn. That one shotted them?
She's right. Okay.
Um
going to zap the Shelesty there.
Give him some room to work with.
I'm surprised he's not trying to pick
off us pick off our our supports.
Where's he? Oh god.
I need to shield him so he can get the
pizza. Get the pizza. Get the pizza.
Ah, he didn't go to it.
No brainer. No brainer.
Okay, that guy missed.
I tried to lob it. Okay, that's a really
lucky stun.
I'm going to try to hand this off while
he goes for the pizza. Oh, he didn't get
the pizza. That sucks. It's respawned.
I'm going to try to get away here. Oh.
Okay, yeah, this isn't looking great.
Thunder.
Run down on her.
Resources. Oh.
He almost snuck up on me.
Isn't the worst chase starter in the
world?
Okay, that's a good raging.
Now try to make distance.
I'm going to try to conserve stamina to
make use of the on hit speed boost.
All right, where did they go?
They hid from my beam.
Oh, this is really bad.
I forgot how bad this area of the map
is.
I'm going to need that on hit speed.
Thank you.
That's pizza.
Going to make walk.
Uh this is a loop right? Okay, yeah.
So going away from that.
I had to use this obstacle. I'm going to
try to conserve stamina again to use the
on hit speed more effectively.
Going to try to conserve it again.
It ain't looking too good though. We're
going to need some help.
He misfired.
Uh 50/50. Oh.
Juke. Oh no, I juked THE PIZZA. NO.
>> [laughter]
>> I'M SO SORRY.
ALL RIGHT, PHOEBE.
We're going to keep doing these games
because we haven't actually reached
level 300 yet. I'm waiting to see that
pop up in the corner after like
a zap or something.
Hopefully.
Anyway, let's do some generators.
Just while the round is still starting.
You got to be careful of someone getting
dropped early though. Kind of just
looking at the HP bars while I do this.
It doesn't look like anyone is in any
immediate danger. So yeah, let's just
finish up that gen.
And help this person who is pretty
cornered right now. Oh.
That almost hit me.
Okay, nice.
Probably going to try and slow them. I
missed my slow, but we hit someone, so
it's whatever.
Honestly, everyone's helping out a lot
right now. I think while my moves are
especially while my moves are on cool
down, I'm just going to go ahead
get this generator done to help lower
the time and also to XP farm because I
really want to level up this car, but
that's besides the point.
I'm just going to finish up the
generator and then I'll help.
They did just miss a walk speed, so they
shouldn't be pressuring anyone right now
anyway.
Anyway,
where are they?
Ooh.
Going to slow them.
I missed. I got to stop trying to do
this doing all freaking plasma beams,
man.
Oh, they switched off the gen pretty
quickly.
Oh, they're on a new gen now.
Yeah, you know, I'm just going to do the
generators, honestly.
It does not look like anyone is being
pressured very much.
Not very much at all.
Holy yeah, that generator was screwing
me up.
Let's do that.
Finish up that one.
Generator number three, I'm just going
to slow him right now.
And then hot bond to the next generator.
Nobody's actually doing generators in
this lobby, it's pretty refreshing.
Let's go ahead, do that.
One, please. I'm praying on one of these
gen puzzles. Like surely surely I'm
close to level 200 by now, right?
Right?
I did start recording these games like
the moment I was level 199, so I still
might be a like a good amount of XP bar
away.
Ooh, let me uh stop that burning
for you.
And then get back to the generators. I
might be able to finish it right here.
Yeah, I should be able to.
If I am quick enough.
Holy crap.
Wait, I might not be quick enough. Oh,
they just reset. Level 200. There we go,
guys.
It's not click bait anymore. Not level
199. No, no, no, it's level 200 Sekhar.
And he's actually been some pretty fun
games. Another game? No, another
nostalgia game. And I'm really scared to
be a killer in this lobby because if
you've been watching this video
all the people in here are pretty good,
though. The people in here are pretty
good. I have to I have to
I have to lock in here.
Going to have to lock in quite hard.
If I can get an early
jump scare on someone, that'd be really
nice. So
Okay, nice.
We got stealth. Now we can Oh, we have
to get that earlier.
Yeah, this is really good. This is
really good. Okay, okay.
Come on, use your shower. Use your
shower. You have to.
Okay, I could get stunned here.
Fish him out. Ah, dang it, the Jane like
body blocked.
No, I didn't hit that. Wait. Stop. No. I
didn't get to cancel it.
Okay, wait.
So, just get some chip damage there.
It's a one shot at two.
This Jane's dead.
We have to kill the Jane right now.
I'll try to get a heartless feast damage
boost if possible.
That also gives us some stealth
opportunities. Oh, no, I have the stun
immunity things on me. Ah, dang it.
Okay, I'm still invisible.
Crap. They reacted to my invisibility.
Okay, hold on. Wait. That might be good.
No, that is not good, actually.
Oh, I still got knocked off.
Okay, that's a guaranteed hit. We got
builder man. That is a really good fish
out of the water. Crap, bro.
Okay, wait.
I guess this miss.
It's a really good opportunity.
This guy might be act blocked. He
doesn't. Crap.
I'm getting a lot of chip damage, but
nothing's sticking yet.
Here we go.
I'm going to have to focus on the shed
now
or the building.
Wait. Okay, this is like if I hit this
mini game, he's dead.
He's got to be dead, right? One one more
in one.
One more in one.
No, how much HP is he? How much HP is
he? Throw that in the air. No.
Wait, I'm stealth.
Okay.
It's a gamble.
Nice gamble. Nice gamble.
He's stuck. He's stuck.
This is really good.
This is unbelievably good.
Okay, nice. Okay, come on. Win the mini
game. Win the mini game. Win the MINI
GAME. YES.
OKAY. OH MY GOSH, BRO.
OKAY, WAIT. SO, send that up there.
All right, no hits. I'm going to jump
scare that hot dog celestial over there.
Okay, what the
Just let him self.
Might block.
Oh wait, what? Okay. Just ran into it.
Oh my gosh, you're a abuser, bro.
All right, whatever.
Throw that up there.
All right, no hits.
We got to hit there.
Yeah, we got to reset the chase somehow.
Let's go up to the J and actually.
They're kind of out of position.
That hopeless is really annoying.
That was a really good slash.
I got to land 100 speeds, man. I got to
get some stealth plays.
Oh. Oh my gosh, wait. No, I messed up
the mini game. Wait. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
>> [laughter]
>> That charge is so good, bro.
Yes, I'm stunning you. I'm stunning you.
I'm stunning you.
Come on. Come on.
Damage wrist.
HIT. NO.
I DON'T THINK THEY'LL BE ABLE TO GET
THERE IN TIME. OKAY, WAIT. I GOT TO
I got to speed on this.
Oh my gosh.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on. They're one shot, one shot, one
shot.
No, if they loop back around. They don't
loop back around, they don't loop back
around.
Come on.
Come on, come on, COME ON. OH MY GOSH.
OKAY. LET'S GO AFTER the Sheleshki,
Sheleshki.
Is all of them off from the other
survivors?
No,
>> [screaming]
>> I wanted that stealth.
I needed that stealth, bro. I actually
needed that stealth. That would have
been so helpful.
Okay, they might slash soon.
OH MY GOSH. OH MY GOSH. OH MY GOSH, THIS
BLOOD HOOK IS CRAZY. THIS BLOOD HOOK IS
CRAZY.
THEY'RE GOING TO SLASH BOTH, THEY'RE
GOING TO SLASH. I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT
NOW, THEY'RE GOING TO SLASH. NO, don't
block. OH MY GOD.
NO. I needed I needed that stealth. I
needed that stealth.
Don't go over there. Don't go over
there. Don't go over there.
Yes, go over there, go over there. Yes,
I can get the roof, I can get the roof.
Okay, come on. No, don't eat that.
BLOCK.
CRAP.
>> [screaming]
>> NO.
>> [laughter]
[gasps]
>> THIS GUY IS JUST SO ANNOYING, BRO.
YES, I HAVE STEALTH, I have stealth.
Okay, wait. I can do something with
this, I can do something with this. Um
No, they healed enough from the chicken.
Come on. Come on. AH, NO.
>> [screaming]
>> I DIDN'T MEAN TO CRASH INTO THAT, I
MEANT TO GO through there.
Okay.
Calm down for a sec.
NO.
>> [screaming]
>> NO.
PLEASE, I'M MISSING EVERYTHING.
NO.
>> [screaming]
[laughter]
>> NO.
WAIT, THE GUEST, THE GUEST.
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON, COME ON, COME
ON, COME ON.
>> [screaming]
[laughter]
>> OH MY GOSH, BRO. THAT WAS SO CLOSE. I
missed so many moves at the end. Oh my
gosh. That was a good game, though. That
was actually really fun. But
There we go.
>> [music]
[music]